A Guide to the Virginia Railroads records, 1863-1926
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Virginia Railroads records, 1863-1926
Library of Virginia
54170
.175 cubic feet (1 box).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Purchased
Scope and Content
Records, 1863-1926, for various railroads operating in Virginia consisting of articles of agreement, bills of lading, correspondence, envelopes, fliers, order forms, overcharge claims, receipts, and tickets regarding the operations and business of various railroads in Virginia, including the Baltimore and Ohio, the Norfolk and Western, and the Richmond and Danville Railroads.
Contents List
- Baltimore and Ohio Railroad Company, 1873, 1887, 1913 (Folder 1)
- Norfolk and Western Railway Company, 1884, 1912-1913, 1926 (Folder 2)
- Orange, Alexandria, and Manassas Railroad, 1871 (Folder 3)
- Richmond and Danville Railroad, 1863, 1889 (Folder 4)
- Richmond and York River Railroad, 1873 (Folder 5)
- Shenandoah Valley Railroad Company, 1889 (Folder 6)
- Tidewater Railway Company, 1906 (Folder 7)
- Valley Railroad Company, no date (Folder 8)
- Virginia Midland Railroad (Folder 9)
- Virginian Railroad Company, no date (Folder 10)
- Waltham Railroad Watches, 1911 (Folder 11)
- Washington City, Virginia Midland, and Great Southern Railroad, 1873, no date (Folder 12)